AMOS GICHERO

WEB DEVELOPER

(404) 519-3561 amosgichero@gmail.com git hub: gichero amosgichero.com

Profile

I became interested in technology 3 years ago when I quit my job and enrolled into a community college to study computer programming. Since graduating, I have quit my job and enrolled in digitalCrafts an immersive coding bootcamp. I am passionate about technology and currently looking for opportunities in Atlanta. My newly acquired skills and interest in the industry would make me an asset in any organization.

Skills

Web Development

I have learned the following technologies in the past 3 years: Java, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Postgres, Python, SQL, Node, jQuery. I am currently learning react, angular2 and redux.

Experience

Shaw industries

2014-2017

2012-2014

Elutriation operator

Contributed to surpassing yearly records processing recycled carpet. I was consistently recognized for punctuality and working overtime.

puricularity and working overtime

Crete Carriers

Long haul truck driver

Accumulated over 150,000 miles without incidence delivering various goods nationally. Recognized as best new driver in 2013 for the Marietta, Georgia terminal

Education

Digitalcrafts coding bootcamp

2017-2017

Chattahoochee technical college

Marietta, Georgia

Associates degree computer programming

2014-2016

University of Canberra Canberra, Australia

Bachelor business management

2002-2006